flvsoft.com 2009-06-20

# FLV Software - flv encoder, flv converter, flv player, flv downloader

Privacy

Moyea fully respects your privacy right, and is committed to protecting your personal information. Generally, you are not required to provide any personal information for browsing Moyea’s website. For specific purposes, in case you provide your name, sex, category and number of credentials, date of birth, country, E-mail box, telephone, address and other similar personal information that are required for registration or reading E-information by voluntarily filling in forms, you will be deemed having understood and accepted the use of your personal information and agreed that Moyea uses your personal information for the specific purposes.

Moyea is committed to keeping your personal information secret and will not sell them at any time under any circumstance, that is to say, we will fulfill our obligations to you and it will not use the information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. However, Moyea may provide certain of your personal information to law executive organs and government authorities as regards to their request; and it may disclose certain of your personal information within a minimal scope when Moyea reasonably thinks it is necessary for protecting Moyea, its customers or the public. You shall have foreseen and agreed to the occurrence of such events when you provide your personal information.

What information do we collect? What do we use it for?

When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you.

How do 3rd party credit card processors protect customer information?

Moyea software uses secure server hosted by SWREG and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer’s personal information including name, address, credit card number credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

SWREG

SWREG is an advanced secure online payment service for software registration that has been in operation since 1987. Moyea Software uses SWREG to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase.

About cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use “cookies”. A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our web site and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.
